myonlineca.in 2019-07-02

# Privacy Policy - MyOnlineCA

This Privacy Policy oversees the way in which myonlineca.in gathers, utilizes, keeps up and reveals data gathered from clients (each, a “Client”) of the https://www.myonlineca.in (“Site”). This protection strategy applies to the Site and all items and administrations offered by MyOnlineCA Technologies Pvt Ltd.

1\. PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION  
We may gather individual recognizable proof data from Users in an assortment of ways, including, yet not constrained to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, put in a request, and regarding different exercises, administrations, highlights or assets we make accessible on our Site. Clients might be requested, as proper, name, email address, postage information, telephone number. Clients may, in any case, visit our Site secretly. We will gather individual ID data from Users just on the off chance that they willfully submit such data to us. Clients can generally reject to supply by and by distinguishing proof data, then again, actually it might keep them from taking part in certain Site related exercises.

2\. NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION  
We may gather individual recognizable proof data from Users in an assortment of ways, including, yet not constrained to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, put in a request, and regarding different exercises, administrations, highlights or assets we make accessible on our Site. Clients might be requested, as proper, name, email address, postage information, telephone number. Clients may, in any case, visit our Site secretly. We will gather individual ID data from Users just on the off chance that they willfully submit such data to us. Clients can generally reject to supply by and by distinguishing proof data, then again, actually it might keep them from taking part in certain Site related exercises.

3\. WEB BROWSER COOKIES Used on MyOnlineCA Web Portal  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

4\. HOW WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION  
MyOnlineCA may gather and utilize Users individual data for the accompanying purposes:

  * To improve client administration – Information you give encourages us react to your client administration demands and bolster needs more proficiently.
  * To customize client experience – We may utilize data in the total to see how our Users as a gathering utilize the administrations and assets gave on our Site.
  * To improve our Site – We may utilize input you give to improve our items and administrations.
  * To process customer payments – We may utilize the data Users give about themselves while putting in a request just to give administration to that request. We don’t impart this data to outside gatherings but to the degree important to give the administration.
  * To run a promotional activity, feedback, or other Site functions – To send Users data they consented to get about points we think will hold any importance with them.
  * To send alerts via emails about due date  – We may utilize the email address to send User data and updates relating to their request. It might likewise be utilized to react to their request, questions, or potentially different solicitations. On the off chance that User chooses to select into our mailing list, they will get messages that may due to date alerts, govt filing update, govt new rules & regulations, related item or administration data, and so on. In the event that whenever the User might want to withdraw from accepting future messages by sending us an email or submit a unsubscribe form at the bottom of emails.

5\. How We Protect Customer Documents & Data Information :  
We always use the High-level Security SSL Certificate on our Web Portal to accept the data from the user. Apart from this, We are using PCI Certified Payment Gateway Companies to accept Online Payments from customers.

Sensitive data like documents of the client exchange over secure email connection’s. Once in a 6 month, we always run a deletion of the completion of projects in the email’s system of the myonlineca team. we never provide any document to any third party without confirmation from the client.

6\. SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

7\. GOOGLE ADSENSE  
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

8\. COMPLIANCE WITH CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT  
Ensuring the security of the exceptionally youthful is particularly critical. Consequently, we never gather or keep up data at our Site from those we really know are under 13, and no piece of our site is organized to draw in anybody under 13.

9\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
myonlineca.in have the prudence to refresh this protection approach whenever. When we do, we will send you an email. We urge Users to habitually check this page for any progressions to remain educated about how we are ensuring the individual data we gather. You recognize and concur that it is your obligation to audit this security approach occasionally and become mindful of changes.

10\. CONTACT US  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

MyOnlineCA Technologies Private Limited  
307, First Floor, Kakrola Housing Complex, Sector 15 Dwarka, Kakrola, New Delhi, Delhi 110078  
Email : mail@myonlineca.in​
